

Behnan Adam

Nationality: Belgian Date of birth: 08/03/1987 Phone number: (+32) 466187887

Home: Assesteenweg 194, 1742 Ternat (Belgium)

ABOUT ME

Dynamic and rigorous, I am ready to put my enthusiasm at the service of your company. I'm worked as an Financial Officer at Media Actie Kuregem Stad vzw for many years and I am characterized by my speed of learning and my taste for a job well done. Contact me in case of opportunity.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Financial Officer

Media Actie Kuregem Stad NPO [16/04/2016 - Current]

Country: Belgium

- General budget management of the nonprofit organization, including preparation and management of wage calculations - Providing information when building the financial files - Complete interim and final reporting - Liaising with funding agencies - Following the financial reports sent by the european partners and ensuring that they're in order - Collaborate with HR and accounting for proper entry of analytical expenses and payroll processing - Managing timelines and agenda for submissions and reports of all grants and interventions - Support to HR and accounting - Supporting the operational teams on financial matters

Teller

Al-jarmakani Exchange Company [01/07/2012 - 15/07/2013]

Country: Syria

- Dealing directly with the customers - Handling cash and executing cash transactions - Handling customer transactions and helping with the related inquiries.

Leader of first aid squad

Syrian Arab Red Cross (SARC) [08/2011 - 05/2012]

Country: Syria

- Responsible for the saftey of the enjured peroson from the scene of the accident until arriving at the hospital - Responsible for the safety of the ambulance team members (Psychological and physical) and all equipments and vehicles - The ability to communicate with all spectrums of the local community within the controls of the internactional committee of the Red Cross (ICRC) and the national law.

Coordinator - Adolescent department in counseling center as psycho-social worker

Syrian Arab Red Crescent with the collaboration of Danish Red Cross (SARC - DRC) [2011]

Country: Syria

- Coordination of the youth team at the counseling center for Iraqi refugees - Responsible for managing the project, including drawing up and monitoring the project budget - Leader of a team of 5 colleagues, guaranteeing effective cooperation and division of tasks - Actively monitor the progress of the project and makeing adjustments if necessary - Providing clear and timely communication with the director to ensure involvement and transparency.

First aid trainer

Syrian Arab Red Cross (SARC) [2011]

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Nonviolent communication

JASPIS [2020]

Website: www.jaspis.be

- Create more connection, harmony and depth in your contacts with others - How to share feelings and how rich our language is to name them - Gain and remain in your strength during challenging situations - how to use assertive communication

Basic social legislation sociocultural course (PC 329)

SOCIARE [2018]

Website: www.sociare.be

- Obligations of the employer - Start and end of the employment contract - Wage, end-of-year bonus - Commuting & mobility - Public holidays and disability - Working hours and flexibility - Part-time work - Holidays - Pregnancy and other suspensions - Casual employees - Training - Work regulations

Web developer (Ruby on Rails)

LE WAGON [2016]

Website: www.lewagon.com

Participated in\IHL\ International Humanitarian Law

Syrian Arab Red Cross (SARC) [2012]

Participated in Business correspondence course

[2007]

Course in Accounting programs (AL Ameen, Bazar, AL Edari, Afak)

[2007]

Degree in Banking & Financial Sciences

Faculty of Economics Aleppo University, Syria [2006]

Country: Syria

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Arabic

Other language(s):

English Dutch

LISTENING C1 READING B2 WRITING C1 LISTENING B2 READING B2 WRITING B1

SPOKEN PRODUCTION B2 SPOKEN INTERACTION B2 SPOKEN PRODUCTION B1 SPOKEN INTERACTION B1

Aramaic language

LISTENING C1 READING B1 WRITING B1

SPOKEN PRODUCTION B2 SPOKEN INTERACTION C1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DIGITAL SKILLS

ICT skills / Microsoft Excel / Microsoft Office / SDWorx / E-Banking - Isabel / EACEA Mobility Tool / platos tijdregistratie / esf vlaanderen / Exact Online / Adobe Photoshop (basic elements) / G-suite (G-mai, G-drive, G-meet) / Ruby on Rails / Begginer HTML/CSS / Corel (CorelDRAW, Corel VideoStudio) / hobby woodworking skills

DRIVING LICENCE

Driving Licence: B